<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>python on Xiangwen Mo</title>
    <link>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in python on Xiangwen Mo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://xiangwenmo.github.io/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 7: CNN model for insect image classification</title>
      <link>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/post/proj-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/post/proj-7/</guid>
      <description>Overview This is the seventh project for BIOSTAT 823 (2020 Fall). This project requires to train a deep learning model to classify beetles, cockroaches and dragonflies using these insect images. (Original images).
I decided to use Yann LeCun&amp;rsquo;s Convolutional Neural Network architecture (LeNet5) and made some adjustment. The most application of it is recoginizing simple digit images, which is kind of what we are trying to do for this problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 6: Dashboard for visualization of PhDs awarded in the US</title>
      <link>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/post/proj-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/post/proj-6/</guid>
      <description>Overview This is the sixth project for BIOSTAT 823 (2020 Fall)
This project requires to download data of PhD awarded in the US and make a dashboard visualization of some aspects of the data.
Dashboard I used dash to create my dashboard by following the online tutorial.
You can check my dashboard here: Dashboard: Doctorate Recipients from US universities
Data I am interested in investigating which fields attract students and the demographics in each field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 5: Use Star Wars API to request Data about SW characters</title>
      <link>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/post/proj-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/post/proj-5/</guid>
      <description>Overview This is the fifth project for BIOSTAT 823 (2020 Fall)
This project requires to use the requests library, download all the people in the Star Wars universe using the Star Wars API. Need to show the name of the oldest character and the titles of films he appears in.
Check API documentation Before request data, we first need to know the patterns of the urls and how to extract the desired information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 4: Convert spotify dataframe to 3NF and create SQL schema</title>
      <link>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/post/proj-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/post/proj-4/</guid>
      <description>Overview This is the fourth project for BIOSTAT 823 (2020 Fall)
This project requires to Create a SQLite3 schema to store spotify data in at least 3rd normal form (3NF) and use an SQL query to find the names of all playlists that contain instrumentals
I used python to do the normalization and stored the transformed dataframe into a SQL database. I&amp;rsquo;ll show how I do it in the following sections:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 3: Visualization about Malaria</title>
      <link>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/post/proj-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/post/proj-3/</guid>
      <description>Overview This is the third project for BIOSTAT 823 (2020 Fall)
This project requires to include 3 informative visualizations about malaria using Python and Malaria Dataset from github.
The detailed solution and codes are in here.
Graph 1: Malaria death by age I used dataset malaria_deaths_age.csv to plot the graph.
  From the graph we can see that young children are more vulnerable to the malaria disease. Especially for under 5 age group, which takes nearly half of the total deaths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Euler&#39;s projects</title>
      <link>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/post/proj-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/post/proj-2/</guid>
      <description>Overview This is the second project for BIOSTAT 823 (2020 Fall)
This project requires to solve three problems from Euler&amp;rsquo;s Project. I choose my two of the problems related to decimals, and one related to prime numbers.
The detailed solution and codes are in here. I will explain my solutions to each of the problems in the following sections:
Problem 7: 10001st prime (420,695) Problem: By listing the first six prime numbers: 2, 3, 5, 7, 11, and 13, we can see that the 6th prime is 13.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>