<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>plotly on Xiangwen Mo</title>
    <link>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/tags/plotly/</link>
    <description>Recent content in plotly on Xiangwen Mo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://xiangwenmo.github.io/tags/plotly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Final-Project: COVID-19 Data Analysis and Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/post/proj-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/post/proj-8/</guid>
      <description>Overview This is the final project for BIOSTAT 823 (2020 Fall). This project focus on two main objectives:
 Covid-19 data visualization that helps users to understand how COVID-19 spread across the world and the United States, and the current pandemic situation we are facing. Use different machine learning methods to predict confirm cases in a next given period. For this project, we have tried three models: SARIMAX model, SVR model, and prophet model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 7: CNN model for insect image classification</title>
      <link>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/post/proj-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/post/proj-7/</guid>
      <description>Overview This is the seventh project for BIOSTAT 823 (2020 Fall). This project requires to train a deep learning model to classify beetles, cockroaches and dragonflies using these insect images. (Original images).
I decided to use Yann LeCun&amp;rsquo;s Convolutional Neural Network architecture (LeNet5) and made some adjustment. The most application of it is recoginizing simple digit images, which is kind of what we are trying to do for this problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 6: Dashboard for visualization of PhDs awarded in the US</title>
      <link>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/post/proj-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiangwenmo.github.io/post/proj-6/</guid>
      <description>Overview This is the sixth project for BIOSTAT 823 (2020 Fall)
This project requires to download data of PhD awarded in the US and make a dashboard visualization of some aspects of the data.
Dashboard I used dash to create my dashboard by following the online tutorial.
You can check my dashboard here: Dashboard: Doctorate Recipients from US universities
Data I am interested in investigating which fields attract students and the demographics in each field.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>